

CONTACT

5, Delmas 40A, Port-au-Prince, Haiti

+509 43 24 18 43

jfenelus@jfenelus.com

linkedin.com/in/jerry-fenelus

EDUCATION

WORDPRESS Plateforme Alphorm 2019 - 2021

DÉVELOPPEUR WEB Plateforme Udemy 2022

SKILLS

Master of JavaScript, PHP, Python,
React Framework, HTML, CSS, JQuery
MySQL data bases,
Versatility, Creativity, Leadership

LANGUAGES

French – Excellent English - Average

Jerry Fenelus

WEB DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

Developer passionate about new technologies and the world of the web, I specialize in front-end and back-end development. Versatile, I master several programming languages including HTML, CSS and JavaScript, etc., and the creation of websites and applications. I know how to identify and understand user needs for better results.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

WEB DESIGNER

MS-CHIC | On line | April 2022 - Present

- Creation of new functionalities
- Communication with customers
- Maintenance and updating of the site

WEB DEVELOPER

Stercha Hotel | Port-au-Prince | March 2022 - Present

- Development of websites
- Development of the visual identity
- Analysis of user needs
- Added new features
- Backup and security management

WEB DEVELOPER

Charcina Hotel | Port-au-Prince | March 2022 - June 2022

- Development of websites
- Development of the visual identity
- Analysis of user needs
- Added new features
- Backup and security management